Ricardo Russ

Full-Stack Web Developer

Atlanta, GA 30126 (404)) 455-4633 Ricardoruss@live.com

Skills

Technical Skills:

Proficient in HTML, CSS (including the Bootstrap, Bulma, and Foundation frameworks), Javascript, and jQuery, My SQL, Node, js and MongoDB.

Learning: React.js, Angular.js, and SASS, Python, C#, and Java

Auxiliary Skills:

Experience in writing legislative documents, working in a busy and customer-service oriented office environment. In addition, I am at an intermediate level and actively improving in both Korean and Russian and have used both in conversational and professional roles.

Experience

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JUNE 2016

Office of Congressman David Scott - Legislative Intern

 Assisted the staff of the office with various tasks including constituent correspondence and the preparation of memos and Congressional Record Statements.

SEPTEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2015

American University Leadership Academy – *Senior Fellow and Communications Director*

 Served with a program dedicated to developing leadership among college students as a communications director and mentor to the students.

Education

FEBRUARY 2020 - MAY 2020

Georgia Tech Full Stack Flex Bootcamp

AUGUST 2013- MAY 2015

American University, Washington, DC - BA in International Studies, Minor in Russian Studies

Side Projects

• You2Brew, an application that allows the user to search for nearby breweries, and once the user has visited the brewery, they can then rate the brewery from 1-5 stars.